frontlinephonics.com 2006-06-16

# Frontline Phonics - Yes. Read.™

** Privacy Policy**

Frontline Phonics (Frontline) is committed to safeguarding your privacy as you use this web site to gather information and/or order our products. By sharing our Privacy Policy, we hope to help you understand how information can create opportunities for our customers, as well as to reassure you that we respect and honor customer requests to restrict and protect personal information. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**

We consider the following, among other things, to be personally identifiable information: first and last name, email address and billing information (e.g. credit card number, expiration date). Additionally, information provided by visitors about the ages of their children in order to receive customized responses to reading assessments, online lessons and other promotions. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information (use of “Cookies”)**

We collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of a software technology called “cookies”. By non-personally identifiable information, we are referring to information about our visitors’ browsers (e.g. Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator or AOL), Internet service providers (e.g. AOL or MSN), pages visited, IP address, date and time of access and other similar information that we track in aggregate form. This information is not shared with any third parties and is used for site statistics or research from our logs. The non-personally identifiable information we track is anonymous and will never be identified with, or lead us back to, any of our visitors.

**Protecting Your Children’s Privacy**

Frontline does not sell products to children. We sell products to adults, who use those products with children. Therefore we do not knowingly accept personal information from any child. If it is brought to our attention that a subscriber is under age, we will immediately remove all personal and identifiable information from our records in compliance with the Online Children’s Privacy Protection Act of 1988. In addition, we will not disclose this information to any other companies. 

**How is Personally Identifiable Information Used?**

Personally identifiable information is primarily used to offer better customer service and to improve communications. These uses include shipping and billing purposes and to deliver product information. This information is also used to 1) provide customized responses to reading assessments and online lessons, 2) enter visitors in sweepstakes and notify sweepstakes winners, and 3) provide visitors with newsletters, reading tips and responses to coaching questions.

Additionally, this personally identifiable information may be used to provide these visitors, via e-mail or other means, information about materials and activities that may be of interest to them, including products or services of third parties. For these reasons, we may share such information with third parties. If you do not wish to receive such information or if you prefer not to have the personally identifiable information you submit shared with third parties, please let us know by either: 1) sending an email to optout@frontlinephonics.com with the words “Opt-Out Request” in the subject line, or 2) sending mail to 1127 South 1680 West, Orem, UT 84058 ATTN: Opt-Out Request. Please include your name, address, and phone number in the correspondence. After the two to three week time period it takes to process your request, your information will no longer be shared.

**Changes to this Policy**

In the future if there is some significant change to this Privacy Policy that affects our usage of your personally identifiable information, we will notify you of those changes on this site or via email. You will then be able to opt-out of this usage if you choose. You should also check this Privacy Policy from time to time for changes.

**Site Security**

When you use secure online forms on our web site (as shown by a solid key or locked padlock icon in the lower right of your browser window), information that you provide is protected with SSL encryption as it is transmitted to our servers. The information is then stored securely offline. We will give out personal information as required by law, for example to comply with a court order or subpoena or to assist in criminal investigations. We may also give out personal information when we deem it advisable in order to protect the safety and security of our sites and visitors to our sites.

We maintain our web site and associated data with technical, physical, and administrative safeguards to protect against loss of data or unauthorized access to or use of data. However, as with any Internet technology, no data can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

**Trademarks**

Frontline Phonics, YESREAD, and the Frontline Phonics logo are trademarks of Frontline Educational Products, LLC. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners.

**Copyrights**

Copyright © 1998-2003 Frontline Educational Products LLC. All rights reserved.

Information on this web site may be downloaded and viewed for personal, non-commercial use only. Any other reproduction of this material by any means is prohibited without the express written consent of Frontline Educational Products, LLC.

E-mail: sales@frontlinephonics.com  
Sales: 1-800-584-READ or 1-800-YES-READ  
International: 1-801-225-2255  
Fax: 1-801-225-2759
